Finding Aid for Vice-President for Development (University of Michigan) records, 1948-[ongoing]
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Vice Presidents
  - Michael Radock, 1960-1983
    - 1963-1980
      - American College Public Relations Association (ACPRA)
        - Committees
          - Executive
            - 1974 (Box 8)
            - 1975 (Box 8)
          - Library Study, 1966-1968 (Box 8)
          - Miscellaneous, 1966-1969 (Box 8)
        - District Conferences
          - General, 1968-1970 (Box 8)
          - Great Lakes District, 1966-1971 (Box 8)
        - Ford Foundation, 1968-1969 (Box 8)
        - General
          - 1964 (Box 8)
          - 1965-1967 (Box 8)
          - 1968-1969 (Box 8)
          - 1976-1978 (Box 8)
          - 1979-1980 (Box 8)
        - Histories, 1963; 1967; 1972 (Box 8)
        - Merger with American Alumni Council, 1969-1972 (Box 8)
          (and name change [to Council for the Advancement and Support of Education (CASE))
        - Negro College Volunteers, 1969-1970 (Box 8)
        - New Trends in Public Relations and Fundraising, 1965-1966 (Box 8)
        - Proposed name change, 1963-1967 (Box 8)
        - Speakers at annual conference, 1965; 2 folders (Box 8)
        - Summer Institutes, 1966-1967 (Box 8)
      - American Council on Education, 1976
        - Educational material prepared by Radock (Box 8)
        - General (Box 8)
      - American Enterprise Institute, 1978 (Box 8)
      - American Nazi Party. (Box 8)
        (See: Jewish Community Center of Detroit)
      - Annual Giving data, 1976-1977 (Box 8)
      - B (Box 8)
      - Bintzer, H. Russell, 1970 (Box 8)
      - Black Action Movement, 1970-1971; 3 folders (Box 8)
      - Broggini, Adrian J., 1970-1973 (Box 8)
      - C (Box 8)
      - California, University of: Development Officers Conference, May 1976 (Box 8)
      - Capital Campaign binder, 1980 (Box 8)
      - Capital Campaign foundation prospects binder, 1980 (Box 8)
      - Capitol Hill Day (Washington, D.C.), 1971 (Box 8)
      - Cobb, Jewel, case, 1975 (Box 9)
      - Committees, 1980 (Box 9)
      - Council for the Advancement and Support of Education. (Box 9)
        (See: American College Public Relations Association (ACPRA))
      - Delaware, University of, 1976-1978 (Box 9)
      - Detroit Press Club Foundation, 1972-1975 (Box 9)
      - Development Council, 1980 (Box 9)
      - East Asian Studies fundraising, 1973-1975 (Box 9)
      - Eastern Illinois University, 1972 (Box 9)
      - Esch, Congressman Marvin, 1975-1976 (Box 9)
      - Fellowship of Christian Athletes, 1971 (Box 9)
      - Fleming, Robben, 1968-1978 (Box 9)
      - Flint campus, 1973-1975 (Box 9)
      - Flint campus scrapbook, 1965-1966 (Box 9)
      - Ford, Gerald, 1973-1974 (Box 9)
      - Frantzreb and Associates, 1963-1966 (Box 9)
      - Freedman, Noel, 1973-1975 (Box 9)
      - Fundraising at the University of Michigan--1970 study (Box 9)
      - Goebel, Paul, 1977-1978 (Box 9)
      - Hathaway (John) communication, 1976 (Box 9)
      - Higher Education
        - 1964 (Box 9)
        - 1967 (Box 9)
      - Highways Safety Research Institute (HRSI), 1967-1972 (Box 9)
      - I (Box 9)
      - Idea of Michigan (fundraising brochure) (Box 9)
      - Internal communications, 1966-1970 (Box 9)
      - Investment in Private Support for the, 1980s; 1979 (Box 9)
      - Jewish Community Center of Detroit, 1964-1965 (Box 9)
        [re American Nazi Party]
      - Kent State University, 1963-1967 (Box 9)
      - L, 1970-1974 (Box 9)
      - Michigan State University, 1970-1973 (Box 9)
      - Morgan-O'Leary Fund, 1972-1973 (Box 9)
      - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1974-1975 (Box 9)
      - National Science Foundation, 1972-1973 (Box 9)
      - National Resources Review Committee, 1970 (Box 9)
      - Operation Michigan, 1964 (Box 9)
      - President's Dinners, 1973-1975 (Box 9)
      - President's House, 1973 (Box 9)
      - Public Relations Society of America, 1964-1974 (Box 9)
      - Q, 1964-1979 (Box 9)
      - Quaal, Ward, 1970-1973 (Box 10)
        [see also: Sesquicentennial Committee]
      - Regents-Alumni Scholar Program, 1969-1975 (Box 10)
      - Radock, Michael--personal
        - Scrapbook, 1965-1966 (Box 10)
        - Speeches and articles, 1973-1975 (Box 10)
      - Sesquicentennial Committee
        - General, 1963-1967 (Box 10)
        - Quaal, Ward, 1964-1967 (Box 10)
        - Subcommittee on Public Relations, 1967 (Box 10)
        - WCBN, 1970-1972 (Box 10)
        - WUOM, 1971-1973 (Box 10)
        - $55 Million Campaign--National Executive Committee notebook, 1965 (Box 10)
        - Vietnam, 1965 (Box 10)
    - 1973-1983
      (primarily 1977-1981)
      - External correspondence
        - Alphabetical (primarily 1977), 1967-1978
          - A-L (Box 10)
          - M-S (Box 10)
          - T-Z (Box 10)
        - Alphabetical (primarily 1978), 1975-1978
          - M-P (Box 10)
        - Chronological, 1978
          - January-June (Box 10)
          - July-December (Box 10)
        - Alphabetical, 1979
          - A-K (Box 10)
          - L-Z (Box 10)
        - Alphabetical, 1980
          - A-L (Box 10)
          - M-Z (Box 10)
        - Alphabetical, 1981 (Box 11)
      - Internal correspondence
        - Chronological
          - 1979
            - January-June (Box 11)
            - July-December, 2 folders (Box 11)
        - Chronological
          - 1980
            - January-June, 2 folders (Box 11)
            - July-December (Box 11)
          - 1981 (Box 11)
      - Unit correspondence (units reporting to vice-president)
        - Alumni Records, 1977-1981 (Box 11)
        - Broadcasting, 1979-1981 (Box 11)
        - Development, 1980-1981 (Box 11)
        - Foundation Relations Office, 1976 (Box 11)
        - Health Science Relations, 1980-1981 (Box 11)
        - Information Services, 1980-1981 (Box 11)
        - Publications, 1980-1981 (Box 11)
        - State and Community Relations, 1980-1981 (Box 11)
      - Senior Staff Meeting minutes
        - 1969-1975 (Box 11)
          (See: Development Office Topical File--Staff meetings)
        - December 1973-1974 (Box 11)
        - 1975 (Box 11)
        - 1976 (Box 11)
        - 1980 (Box 11)
        - 1981 (Box 11)
        - 1982, 2 folders (Box 12)
      - Reorganization plans (pre-Cosovich) (Box 12)
      - Round-Up
        - 1975 (Box 12)
        - 1976 (Box 12)
        - 1977 (Box 12)
        - 1978 (Box 12)
        - 1980 (Box 12)
        - 1981 (Box 12)
        - 1982, 2 folders (Box 12)
        - 1983, 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Jon Cosovich, 1981-1996
    - Correspondence and memoranda, 1985-1996
      - 1985 (Box 39)
        - August-December (Box 39)
      - 1986
        - January-February (Box 39)
        - March (Box 39)
        - April (Box 39)
        - May-June (Box 39)
        - July-August (Box 39)
        - September-December (Box 39)
      - 1987
        - January-February (Box 39)
        - March-June (Box 39)
        - July (Box 39)
        - August-September (Box 39)
      - 1988
        - January-February (Box 39)
        - March-April (Box 39)
        - May-June (Box 39)
        - July (Box 39)
        - August-September (Box 39)
        - October-December (Box 39)
      - 1989
        - January (Box 39)
        - February-April (Box 39)
        - May-July (Box 39)
        - August (Box 39)
        - September-October (Box 39)
      - 1990
        - January-February (Box 39)
        - March (Box 39)
        - April (Box 39)
        - May-June (Box 39)
        - July-September (Box 40)
        - October-December (Box 40)
        - Indirect (FYI or CC) (Box 40)
      - 1991
        - January-February (Box 40)
        - March-May (Box 40)
        - June-July (Box 40)
        - September-October (Box 40)
        - November-December 1991 (Box 40)
        - Indirect (FYI or CC) (Box 40)
      - 1992
        - January (Box 40)
        - February-March (Box 40)
        - April-May (Box 40)
        - June-July (Box 40)
        - August-September (Box 40)
        - December (Box 40)
        - Indirect (FYI or CC) (Box 40)
      - 1993
        - January (Box 40)
        - February-March (Box 40)
        - April (Box 40)
        - May (Box 40)
        - June-July (Box 40)
        - August-October (Box 40)
        - November-December (Box 40)
        - Indirect (FYI or CC) (Box 40)
      - 1994
        - January-February (Box 40)
        - March-April (Box 40)
        - May-June (Box 40)
        - July-August (Box 40)
        - September-December (Box 40)
        - Indirect (FYI or CC) (Box 40)
      - 1995
        - January-June (Box 40)
        - July-December (Box 40)
      - 1996
        - February-July (Box 40)
    - Events, 1994-1995
      - Henry Johnson retirement, 1995 (Box 41)
      - Richard Kennedy retirement, 1994
        - Budget and planning, 4 folders (Box 41)
        - Program and invitations (Box 41)
      - Jonas Salk/ March of Dimes Polio Vaccine Commemoration, 1995
        - Articles (Box 41)
        - Planning, 4 folders (Box 41)
        - Program and invitation (Box 41)
    - Gerald Ford, 1983-1994
      - Center for Public Affairs, 1984-1989 (Box 41)
      - Correspondence, general, 1988-1989 (Box 41)
      - Gerald Ford Library, gifts and pledges, 1985-1988 (Box 41)
      - Meetings, 1983-1994
        - Agendas, 1983-1994 (Box 41)
        - Correspondence and miscellaneous
          - 1983 (Box 41)
          - 1984, 3 folders (Box 41)
          - 1985, 3 folders
          - 1987 (Box 41)
          - 1993 (Box 41)
    - Presidential search, 1988-1996 (Box 42)
      - Academic Presidency, general, 1996 (Box 42)
      - Lee Bollinger Appointment, news releases and articles, 1996 (Box 42)
      - James Dudestadt retirement, 1996
        - Articles (Box 42)
        - Party, reception and gift planning
          - General (Box 42)
          - Invitation lists (Box 42)
          - Faculty Awards and Fellowship listings, 1988-1996 (Box 42)
      - Search Process
        - Articles, 1994-1996; 2 folders (Box 42)
        - Candidate data summaries (Box 42)
        - News releases, mailings and correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 42)
        - Presentations-search models and process proposal (Box 42)
        - Regents forums, 1995-1996
          - General (Box 42)
          - Detroit (Box 42)
          - Grand Rapids, 2 folders (Box 42)
    - Topical, 1981-1996
      - Business and Finance Management Institute, 1993 (Box 42)
      - COMMCOOR/ Executive Committees Retreat, 1994-1996
        - September 1994 (Box 42)
        - November 1994 (Box 42)
        - January 1995 (Box 42)
        - March 1995 (Box 42)
        - May 1995 (Box 42)
        - October 1995 (Box 42)
        - January 1996 (Box 42)
        - May 1996 (Box 42)
      - Duderstadt, James, 1988-1994
        - Biographical profile, 1993 (Box 42)
        - Calendars and itineraries, 1989-1994 (Box 42)
        - Campaign materials, 1989-1994 (Box 42)
        - Correspondence and memoranda, 1988-1994 (Box 42)
      - Itineraries, 1990-1995
        - 1990, 2 folders (Box 42)
        - 1991 (Box 42)
        - 1992 (Box 42)
        - 1993 (Box 43)
        - 1994 (Box 43)
        - 1995 (Box 43)
      - Leadership Gifts reviews, 1992-1994 (Box 43)
      - Presidential Dinners, 1992-1994 (Box 43)
      - Shapiro, Harold T., 1981-1987
        - Calendars and meeting agendas, 1983-1985 (Box 43)
        - Campaign materials, 1984-1987 (Box 43)
        - Correspondence and memoranda, December 1981-June 1984 (Box 43)
        - Gift history, as of, 1987 (Box 43)
      - State Strategy Group, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1995-1996 (Box 43)
      - Visitors Group, 1995-1996
        - Agendas and meeting materials, March 1995-March 1996 (Box 43)
        - Correspondence and memoranda, May 1995-May 1996 (Box 43)
        - Member lists and information, 1995-1996 (Box 43)
      - Women in Higher Education Management listing, 1993 (Box 43)
- Development Office, 1943-1992
  The Development Office subgroup, dating from 1948 to 1984 and measuring 11 linear feet, consists of four series: Foundation Relations, a Topical File, and Photographs and Staff Files. Records within the series are arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - Foundation Relations
    The Foundation Relations Office records consist of chronological correspondence files for the period 1976 to 1980; committee, conference, and project files from 1973 to 1983; and schools and colleges files. The schools and colleges files contain information on various university units' fundraising and grant seeking attempts, and their dealings with the Foundation Relations Office. These files reflect the growing concern for centralized coordination of university-wide development campaigns and the difficulties encountered by the Foundation Relations Office in maintaining control over individual units' campaigns.
    - Chronological
      - 1976-1977 (Box 13)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 13)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 13)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 13)
    - Committees
      - Foundation Relations Study Committee
        - Charter (Box 13)
        - Foundation Advisory Council (Box 13)
        - Geographical Analysis (Box 13)
        - Meetings
          - November 22, 1974 (Box 13)
          - October 30, 1975 (Box 13)
          - 1976 (Box 13)
          - 1977 (Box 13)
          - October 13, 1978 (Box 13)
          - 1979 (Box 13)
          - October 11 (Box 13)
        - Membership
          - General (Box 13)
          - 1977-1980
            - Aymond, Al (Box 13)
            - Barbour, Fleming (Box 13)
            - Blackerby, Philip E (Box 13)
            - Campbell, Mary Alice (Box 13)
            - Forsythe, Carl S (Box 13)
            - Gram, H. James (Box 13)
            - Hunting, David D (Box 13)
            - Lochner, Kenneth M (Box 13)
            - Lundahl, Arthur B (Box 13)
            - MacRae, Robert H (Box 13)
            - Parfet, Ray T (Box 13)
            - Richardson, Dean (Box 13)
            - Schwartz, Alan E (Box 13)
            - Scott, Will (Box 13)
            - Slykhouse, George J (Box 13)
            - Upjohn, E. Gifford (Box 13)
          - 1980-1983
            - Bixby, H. Glenn (Box 13)
            - Palmer, H. Bruce (Box 13)
            - Roberts, Robert (Box 13)
            - Theodoroff, James (Box 13)
            - Williams, Brymer (Box 13)
    - Conferences
      - Conference of Michigan Foundations [renamed Council of Michigan Foundations in 1976]
        - Annual conference
          - (1st), 1973 (Box 13)
          - (2nd), 1974 (Box 13)
          - (3rd), 1975 (Box 13)
      - Council of Michigan Foundations
        - Annual conference
          - (4th), 1976 (Box 13)
          - (5th), 1977 (Box 13)
          - (6th), 1978 (Box 13)
          - (7th), 1979 (Box 13)
          - (8th), 1980 (Box 13)
    - Projects [funding for]
      - Amphibian Facility, 1979 (Box 13)
      - Geology, 1980 (Box 13)
      - Gerontology, 1979 (Box 13)
      - Highway Safety Research Institute, 1980 (Box 13)
      - Insitute for Social Research, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
      - Law School Addition (Box 13)
      - Michigan Union project, 1980 (Box 13)
      - Psycholopysiology Laboratory, 1978-1979 (Box 13)
    - Schools and Colleges files, 1970-1983
      - Architecture and Urban Planning
        - Malcomson, Reginald, 1973 (Box 13)
        - Paraskevopoulos Fund, 1976 (Box 13)
        - Policies on housing for the elderly, 1979-1981 (Box 13)
      - Architecture, College of
        - Consultant information, 1971-1983 (Box 13)
      - Art School
        - China Exchange Project, 1981-1982 (Box 13)
        - Consultant information, 1974-1980 (Box 13)
        - Korten Student Awareness Project, 1980 (Box 13)
      - Athletic Department
        - Consultant information, 1972-1978 (Box 13)
      - Biological Research Station
        - General, 1971-1980; 1 folders (Box 13)
        - General, 1971-1980; 1 folders (Box 14)
        - Campaign plans, 1975-1978 (Box 14)
        - Meetings and correspondence--David Gates, 1977-1983 (Box 14)
      - Botanical Gardens
        - General (Box 14)
      - Business Administration, School of
        - General, 1975-1981 (Box 14)
        - Consultant information, 1971-1980 (Box 14)
        - Phelps Fund, 1977 (Box 14)
      - Centers and Institutes (University of Michigan)
        - Amphibian Facility, 1979 (Box 14)
        - Biological Station, 1982 (Box 14)
        - Gerontology, Institute of, 1981-1983 (Box 14)
        - Human Growth and Development, Center for, 1981 (Box 14)
        - North Campus Child Care, 1980 (Box 14)
        - Population Studies, Center for, 1979-1982 (Box 14)
        - Pound House Children's Center, 1982 (Box 14)
        - Russian and East European Studies, Center for, 1982 (Box 14)
        - Science and Technology, Institute of: Great Lakes Research Division, 1982 (Box 14)
        - Simpson Memorial Institute, 1982 (Box 14)
      - Cultural Relations
        - China/University of Michigan Research Fellow Exchange, 1981 (Box 14)
      - Dearborn Campus
        - Advisory Committee, 1976 (Box 14)
        - Consultant information, 1971-1979 (Box 14)
        - Music, School of, 1981 (Box 14)
        - Program information, 1980-1981 (Box 14)
      - Dentistry, School of
        - Consultant information, 1976-1979 (Box 14)
      - Education, School of
        - Center for the Study of Higher Education
          - General, 1981 (Box 14)
          - Norman Harris Fund, 1977 (Box 14)
        - Consultant information, 1976-1979 (Box 14)
        - Funds, 1977-1978 (Box 14)
        - Program information, 1982 (Box 14)
        - Wagaw, Teshome G., 1976 (Box 14)
      - Engineering, College of
        - Academic Affairs: Detroit Area Pre-College Engineering Program (DAPCEP) funding, 1981 (Box 14)
        - Aerospace: Project Scope, 1982 (Box 14)
        - Consultant information, 1971-1979 (Box 14)
        - Engineering Industrial Support Program (EISP) Project, 1980 (Box 14)
        - George Landes Memorial Fund, 1981-1982 (Box 14)
        - Humanities Seminar Series, 1981-1982 (Box 14)
        - Papalambros, Panos, 1980 (Box 14)
        - Schneider, Robert (Computer Related Areas), 1981 (Box 14)
        - Siebert Fund, 1976-1977 (Box 14)
        - Special Funds, 1971-1979 (Box 14)
      - Flint Campus
        - Consultant information, 1974-1980 (Box 14)
        - Microwave Link Project, 1980 (Box 14)
        - Presidents Club, 1981 (Box 14)
        - Reports, 1974-1976 (Box 14)
      - Fresh Air Camp
        - General, 1978-1979 (Box 14)
      - Graduate School (Rackham)
        - International Studies Endowment, 1980-1981 (Box 14)
        - Program information (Box 14)
      - Institute for Social Research
        - Foundation support, 1982 (Box 14)
        - Gerontology
          - Conference on Older Working Women, 1982 (Box 14)
          - Services to Families of Older Persons, 1982 (Box 14)
        - State of Michigan Survey, 1981 (Box 14)
      - Law School
        - General, 1973-1981 (Box 14)
        - Consultant information, 1971-1979 (Box 14)
        - Jones, Rob, 1974-1980 (Box 14)
      - Libraries
        - Bentley Historical Library, 1981-1983 (Box 14)
        - Clements Library, 1976-1979 (Box 14)
        - Ford, Gerald R., Library, 1977-1981 (Box 14)
        - Graduate Library Preservation Program, 1981-1982 (Box 14)
      - Library Science, School of
        - Consultant information, 1972-1982 (Box 15)
        - Endowed Chair/Endowment, 1976-1977 (Box 15)
      - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of
        - Astronomy, 1981-1983 (Box 15)
        - Center for Near Eastern/African Studies, 1978-1979 (Box 15)
        - Chemistry Building solicitations, 1980 (Box 15)
        - Consultant information, 1970-1980 (Box 15)
        - Departmental programs, 1977-1983 (Box 15)
        - Economics Department building project, 1981-1982 (Box 15)
        - German Department, 1982 (Box 15)
        - Horticultural Therapy Project, 1981 (Box 15)
        - Institute for Public Policy Studies: Watergate Project, 1981-1982 (Box 15)
        - Internship Program, 1979-1980 (Box 15)
        - Kelsey Museum, 1973-1974 (Box 15)
        - Martin Luther Conference, 1982-1983 (Box 15)
        - Muir, Roy, 1979-1981 (Box 15)
        - Oncley, J.L., Lectureship, 1980 (Box 15)
        - Political Science Encomium Fund, 1973-1976 (Box 15)
        - Renaissance High Leadership Project, 1981-1982 (Box 15)
        - Rhodes, Don L., Memorial Fund, 1980-1981 (Box 15)
      - Medical Center
        - General, 1973-1976 (Box 15)
        - Consultant information, 1972-1980 (Box 15)
        - Institute for the Study of Mental Retardation and Related Disabilities, 1976 (Box 15)
        - Presidents Club prospects, 1977-1979 (Box 15)
        - Summary of development projects, 1974 (Box 15)
      - Medical School
        - General, 1977-1982 (Box 15)
        - Biological Engineering, 1977-1978 (Box 15)
        - Medicine and Medical Practice course design, 1982 (Box 15)
      - Mental Health Research Institute
        - Layman Allen--Math Games, 1976-1982 (Box 15)
      - Music, School of
        - General, 1981-1982 (Box 15)
        - Capital Developments, 1977 (Box 15)
        - Congress of Women/Keyboard Institute, 1981 (Box 15)
        - Consultant information, 1971-1978 (Box 15)
        - Development Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 15)
        - Swanson, Bessie, 1976 (Box 15)
        - Vocal Arts Center, 1978 (Box 15)
      - Natural Resources, School of
        - General, 1980-1982 (Box 15)
        - Consultant information, 1973-1979 (Box 15)
        - Landscape Architecture, 1976 (Box 15)
        - Program information, 1980-1982 (Box 15)
        - Teams Project--Camp Filibert Roth, 1981-1982 (Box 15)
      - Pharmacy, College of
        - Consultant information, 1972-1982 (Box 15)
        - Kellogg proposal, 1981-1982 (Box 15)
      - Public Health, School of
        - Consultant information, 1970-1981 (Box 15)
        - Program information, 1976 (Box 15)
      - Scholarships and fellowships
        - General, n.d. (Box 15)
        - Out-of-state scholarship fundraising, 1977-1981 (Box 15)
      - University Hospital
        - General, 1976-1981 (Box 16)
        - Division of Geriatric Medicine, 1981 (Box 16)
        - Hospital Administrators Annual Fund, 1976-1978 (Box 16)
        - Human Resources Planning Program, 1981 (Box 16)
      - Women's centers and programs
        - Continuing Education for Women--Women in Science Program, 1980-1981 (Box 16)
  - Topical File, 1950-1987
    The records in the Development Office Topical File, divided into Historical Files and an Alphabetical Subject File, reflect the curious history of this unit. The Development Office was originated and funded by the Development Council, a group of volunteer alumni organized to raise funds to support the university. Only after the initiation of the $55 Million Campaign in 1964 did this office become clearly associated with the vice president, developing into a central clearing office for all university fundraising projects.
    - Historical files
      - Histories of development program and of specific appeals, 1952-1977 (Box 16)
      - Capital Gifts Program literature, 1950-1960 (Box 16)
      - Class appeals [sample letters]
        - 1957-1963 [classes: 1890-1930] (Box 16)
        - 1962-1966 (Box 16)
      - Class funds
        - Correspondence and records of donations [classes: ], 1899-1939 (scattered) (Box 16)
        - History of class funds [classes of ], 1876-1964; 1970 (Box 16)
      - Class gifts
        - Class of ["Onus" sculpture--North Campus Commons], 1961 (Box 16)
      - Cooley Memorial Project--College of Engineering
        - Correspondence--Kersting, Brown and Company, 1948 (Box 16)
        - "A Survey of Fund Raising Resources and a Plan of Campaign" by Kersting, Brown and Company, 1948 (Box 16)